<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Seoul, Korea</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">The Vibrant City</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_location">Attractions</string>
    <string name="menu_restaurant">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="menu_hotel">Hotels</string>

    <string name="intro_blub">
        Seoul is a city filled with vibrancy, consisting of both traditional Korean culture and modern culture, making it a popular
        destination among tourists. Seoul is riding a creative wave. The city has become a creative sanctuary for people wanting to make
        their mark on everything from fashion to food to architecture to art.
    </string>

    <string name="hotel_txt0">
        In one of Asia\'s most dynamic and economically powerful cities, the hotel effectively blends comfortable
        elegance with cutting\-edge technology. The famous Peter Remedios designed the interiors, which are a perfect combination
        of East and West, while a large number of world\-class masterpieces light the hotel with top\-notch elegance.
    </string>
    <string name="hotel_txt1">
        JW Marriott Hotel Seoul, a renowned location in the Gangnam District, offers 5\-star elegance amid some of
        South Korea\'s most recognized attractions. Explore South Korea\'s renowned Gangnam District, which is home
        to some of the best shopping, eating, and cultural activities. In a vibrant event venue enhanced by contemporary
        technology, personalized food, and professional planners, you can host faultless meetings, weddings, and social gatherings.
    </string>
    <string name="hotel_txt2">
        Grand InterContinental Seoul Parnas, located in the heart of Gangnam\'s renowned neighborhood, provides
        an exceptional experience for both leisure and business guests. The hotel is next to the COEX Convention and has
        easy access to one of Korea's best retail, leisure, and business complexes.
    </string>
    <string name="hotel_txt3">
        Lotte Hotel Seoul is one of Korea\'s finest 5\-star luxury hotels, ideally located near Myeongdong
        in the heart of Seoul\'s major business area. Four world\-class interior design firms collaborated
        to create 1,015 guest rooms in the Main Tower and Executive Tower.
    </string>
</resources>